tvsmotor.in 2019-05-05

# TVS CORPORATE - xpress service

This privacy policy sets out how TVS Motor and protects any information that you give us when you use this website.

TVS Motor Company is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, and then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement?  
TVS Motor Company may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from January 1, 2018

**We may collect the following information:**

  * name and job title

  * contact information including email address

  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences, and interests

  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:**

  * Internal record keeping.

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.

  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.  
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.  
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

Controlling your personal information

 **You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:**

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes

  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at online@tvsmotor.com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to online@tvsmotor.com  
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above E-mail address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. 

**Google Play Privacy Policy:**

We agree that our products that are available through Google Play will protect your privacy and legal rights. As you provide us with, or our product accesses or uses your usernames, passwords, or other login or personal information, we agree to make you aware that the information that is available with us will be provided with legally adequate privacy notice and protection. Further, our product may only use that information for the limited purposes for which we have been given permission to do so. 

Our product will store your personal or sensitive information securely and only for as long as it is needed. However, on any scenario, if you opt into a separate agreement with us which will allow us to store or use personal or sensitive information directly related to our products, then the terms of that separate agreement will govern the use of such information. 

Also, If you provide Google Account information, we will only use that information to access your Google Account when, and for the limited purposes for which we have been given your permission to do so. 

**If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:**

Company Name: TVS Motor Company   
Address: TVS Motor Company  
Jayalakshmi Estates V Floor  
8, Haddows Road Chennai - 600006  
Ph: 044-28272233 Fax: 044-28257121  
E‐Mail ID: Online.Support@tvsmotor.com
